Broadcast Center Recordings, circa 1980-2017: Finding Aid AC362
University Archives
- Series 3: Broadcast Center Recordings, 1990 January 18-1999 December 3; 37 boxes
  - Princeton History, 1995 April 26; 1734; 1 box (Box 41)
    Shots of letter, interview with President Harold Shapiro Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 April 26; 1735; 1 box (Box 41)
    Interview with President Harold Shapiro, President Shapiro's discussion with students. Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 April 26; 1736; 1 box (Box 41)
    Harold Shapiro's discussion with students, Interview with professor Painter Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 April 26; 1737; 1 box (Box 41)
    Interview with Prof. Painter, Firestone library B-Roll Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 April 26; 1738; 1 box (Box 41)
    Archive dept. walk through Pagano/Juliano
  - Lecture, 1995 August 09; 1166; 1 box (Box 54)
    Tali Mendelberg News Piece Master
  - Defining Moments, 1995 December 01; 1183; 1 box (Box 4)
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1995 December 06; 135; 1 box (Box 11)
    Bonner
  - Lecture, 1995 February 07; 110; 1 box (Box 11)
    Jane Whitman
  - Pierro Final Project, 1995 February 20; 1240; 1 box (Box 30)
  - Princeton History, 1995 February 20; 1694; 1 box (Box 40)
    Professor Warren interview Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 February 20; 1695; 1 box (Box 40)
    Professor Warren interview. S. Georgia Nugent Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 February 20; 1696; 1 box (Box 40)
    S. Georgia interview Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 February 20; 1699; 1 box (Box 40)
    End of seminar with president, walk over to archive dept., intro with archivist Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 February 20; 1700; 1 box (Box 40)
    Explanation about archive Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 February 20; 1702; 1 box (Box 40)
    President Shapiro's Student Seminar Pagano/Juliano
  - President Shapiro, 1995 February 20; 1703; 1 box (Box 40)
  - Princeton History, 1995 February 25; 1698; 1 box (Box 40)
    President seminar over dinner Pagano/Juliano
  - MLK Day, 1995 January 16; 196; 1 box (Box 11)
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1704; 1 box (Box 40)
    Professor Howarth interview Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1705; 1 box (Box 40)
    Professor Howarth interview. Professor Ziolkawski interview Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1706; 1 box (Box 40)
    Professor Ziolkawski interview. Greenspan Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1707; 1 box (Box 41)
    Professor Ziolkawski interview Greenspan. Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1708; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1709; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1710; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1711; 1 box (Box 41)
    President Shapiro Student Seminar Maher/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 March 06; 1712; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1739; 1 box (Box 41)
    Interview with "Jeff" (student) Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1740; 1 box (Box 41)
    Cindy Wong interview Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1741; 1 box (Box 41)
    Cindy Wong interview, interview with "John"(student) Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1742; 1 box (Box 41)
    Interview with "John"(student), interview with female student Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1743; 1 box (Box 41)
    Interview with "Colleen"(student), President Shapiro's Student Seminar at President's home. Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1744; 1 box (Box 41)
    President Shapiro's Student Seminar at President's house, exterior shots Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1745; 1 box (Box 41)
    President Shapiro's Student Seminar at President's home Pagano/Juliano
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1746; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1747; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1748; 1 box (Box 41)
  - Princeton History, 1995 May 01; 1749; 1 box (Box 41)
    President Shapiro's Student Seminar at the President's house Pagano/Juliano
  - Lecture, 1995 May 09; 1221; 1 box (Box 55)
    Jonathan Brown 101 McCormick
  - Lecture, 1995 May 11; 156; 1 box (Box 11)
    Philippe Nozieres. Is many body physics a settled issue? Physics/Donald Ross Hamilton Lectures
  - Baccalaureate, 1995 May 28; 109; 1 box (Box 11)
    Speaker: Jane Alexander
  - Commencement, 1995 May 30; 124; 1 box (Box 11)
  - Whig Hall 1995 Renovation Continuous Loop, 1995 July 01; 1324; 1 box (Box 56)
    DVD
    Edited in November 2009
  - Princeton and World War 2, 1995 November 09; 143; 1 box (Box 11)
    Richard Challener
  - Lecture, 1995 November 09; 150; 1 box (Box 11)
  - 250th campaign kickoff Press Conference, 1995 November 09; 189; 1 box (Box 11)
  - World War Two, 1995 November 09; 1119; 1 box (Box 25)
  - Lecture, 1995 November 10; 112; 1 box (Box 11)
    Jeremiah Ostriker on Cosmological Reflections: 250th campaign
  - Global telecommunications convergence and the future of media, 1995 November 10; 117; 1 box (Box 11)
    250th campaign
  - Lecture, 1995 November 10; 1255; 1 box (Box 55)
    John Miller Slides
  - Campus Shots, 1995 October 02; 1632; 1 box (Box 38)
    Students acting/speaking about University, tight shot of students taking exam, cover shots of empty room, bleachers, daily Princetonian, Nassau st. University entrance/st. and people, chapel shot.
  - Lecture, 1995 October 19; 1209; 1 box (Box 55)
    Robert Davies McCosh 50
  - Greenspan, 1995 October 20; 1179; 1 box (Box 29)
    Greenspan Tape #1: Students biking/walking, group at Murray Dodge
  - Greenspan, 1995 October 20; 1180; 1 box (Box 29)
    Greenspan Tape# 2: Dancing class, class cover shots, students behind computers, students playing games and conversing, archival photo stills.
  - Greenspan, 1995 October 20; 1181; 1 box (Box 29)
    Greenspan Tape #3: Minority students singing in a large group
  - Greenspan, 1995 October 20; 1182; 1 box (Box 29)
    Greenspan Tape #4: Minority students singing in a large group
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1995 September 21; 138; 1 box (Box 11)
    Lawrence Stone The place of Princeton in the history of higher education
  - The Role of Princeton in the History of Higher Education, 1995 September 21; 1193; 1 box (Box 55)
    Professor Stone 250th Anniversary Lecture
  - Princeton University archive stills and newspaper clippings, 1995 September 24; 1612; 1 box (Box 38)
    Rainey/Hooper
  - Princeton University archive stills and newspaper clippings, 1995 September 24; 1613; 1 box (Box 38)
    zoom in and outs. Rainey/Hooper
  - Princeton University archive stills and newspaper clippings, 1995 September 24; 1614; 1 box (Box 38)
    zoom in and outs/pans/tilts. Rainey/Hooper
  - Archival library and percussion players, 1995 September 24; 1616; 1 box (Box 38)
    Cover shots of books taken off the shelf and opened up, archival shots, Declaration Of Independence cover shots, percussion players at museum. Rainey/Hooper
  - Princeton University archive stills and newspaper clippings, 1995 September 25; 1615; 1 box (Box 38)
  - Campus Shots, 1995 September 25; 1617; 1 box (Box 38)
    Percussion at museum, shot of walkway during rain, indoor of Prospect House. Rainey/Hooper
  - Campus Shots, 1995 September 26; 1619; 1 box (Box 38)
    Dance class, outdoor/indoor shots looking into Rabb's class. Rainey/Hooper
  - Campus Shots, 1995 September 27; 1621; 1 box (Box 38)
    Albert Raboteau and Will Howarth class lecture/class cover shots, people walking around Chapel. Rainey/Hooper
  - Campus Shots, 1995 September 27; 1622; 1 box (Box 38)
    Princeton University's Archival shots. Rainey/Hooper
  - Campus Shots, 1995 September 28; 1625; 1 box (Box 38)
    Students going under arch, students hanging out on grass, Aaron Lemonick class lecture, women's crew shots. Rainey/Hooper
  - Campus Shots, 1995 September 29; 1627; 1 box (Box 38)
    Richardson Hall outdoor shots, gargoyle shots, students hanging out outdoors, student reading a book to camera, Nassau Hall outdoor shots. Rainey/Hooper
  - Campus Shots, 1995 September 30; 1628; 1 box (Box 38)
    Student interviewed, Nassau Hall crane shots, Nassau Hall interior with students talking about the hall. Rainey/Hooper
  - Defining Moments, 1995 December 01; 1183; 1 box (Box 62)
    250th Anniversary Back-up DVD Made
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 April 11; 144; 1 box (Box 11)
    Daniel T. Rodgers The social sciences at Princeton
  - The best of Princeton, 1996 April 11; 175; 1 box (Box 11)
    Dance at McCarter 2 tapes
  - 250th Anniversary Lecture, 1996 April 11; 1117; 1 box (Box 25)
    Anthony Grafton and Daniel Rogers
  - Bosnia Talk, 1996 April 24; 1128; 1 box (Box 25)
    Bowl 1
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1546; 1 box (Box 36)
    Dorothy Bedford
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1547; 1 box (Box 36)
    JT Miller
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1548; 1 box (Box 36)
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1549; 1 box (Box 36)
    Howard Shapiro address
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1550; 1 box (Box 36)
    Postcard Ceremony
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1551; 1 box (Box 36)
    Postcard B-Roll, Alexander Hall, Nassau Hall, Archives, Habitat
  - Campus Shots (Spring), 1996 February 03; 1552; 1 box (Box 36)
    Student shots outside Firestone and surrounding area, students conversing over Coke, student volunteers council office shots, student behind computer
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1553; 1 box (Box 36)
    Chapel ceremony - Shots with Shapiro, cover shots, choir shots, Pastor speaking
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1554; 1 box (Box 36)
    Dedication Ceremony of township to the 250th Anniversary of PU: People and live music outside, Harold Shapiro, Mayor Reed, and Ex-Governor Byrne speaking at podium, 250th Anniversary flag
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1555; 1 box (Box 36)
    Bert Malkiel
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1556; 1 box (Box 36)
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1557; 1 box (Box 36)
    Book shots
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 03; 1559; 1 box (Box 37)
    Opening Ceremony Tape 2
  - Lecture, 1996 February 05; 1215; 1 box (Box 55)
    King of Buganda Dodds Auditorium
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 February 07; 134; 1 box (Box 11)
    Ted Ziolkowski
  - Lecture, 1996 February 12; 186; 1 box (Box 11)
    Allen Ginsberg and Gus Van Sant
  - Lecture, 1996 February 16; 146; 1 box (Box 11)
    Bill Bradley
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 February 22; 145; 1 box (Box 11)
    Georgia Nugent Changing faces: The Princeton Student of the 20th century
  - The 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1185; 1 box (Box 29)
    Opening Ceremony
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1558; 1 box (Box 36)
    Opening Ceremony Tape 1
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1560; 1 box (Box 37)
    Opening Ceremony Tape 3
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1561; 1 box (Box 37)
    Opening Ceremony Tape 4
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1562; 1 box (Box 37)
    Opening Ceremony Tape 5
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1563; 1 box (Box 37)
    Opening Ceremony Tape 6
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1564; 1 box (Box 37)
    Opening Ceremony Tape 7
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 February 23; 1683; 1 box (Box 40)
  - Lecture, 1996 February 26; 155; 1 box (Box 11)
    Allen Ginsberg. Clear seeing poetics: New Jersey through the states
  - MLK day, 1996 January 15; 108; 1 box (Box 11)
  - 1996 Baccalaureate, 1996 June 02; 1153; 1 box (Box 27)
    Speaker: Bill Bradley '65
  - Princeton University Commencement, 1996 June 04; 1152; 1 box (Box 27)
    Main camera coverage
  - 1996 Commencement, undated; 1124; 1 box (Box 25)
  - 1996 Commencement, undated; 1137; 1 box (Box 26)
    Beta SP Field Tape 2
  - 1996 Commencement, undated; 1154; 1 box (Box 27)
    Tape 1
  - 1996 Commencement, undated; 1155; 1 box (Box 27)
  - Princeton Commencement 1996, undated; 1156; 1 box (Box 27)
    Ceremony with Commentary of Clinton's address Tape #1
  - 1996 Commencement, undated; 1157; 1 box (Box 27)
    President Clinton's address Tape #1
  - 1996 Commencement, 1996 June 04; 1132; 1 box (Box 55)
    President Clinton and Baker
  - 1996 Commencement, 1996 June 04; 1254; 1 box (Box 55)
    President Clinton Tape #2
  - 1996 Commencement, undated; 1208; 1 box (Box 4)
  - Baccalaureate, 1996 June 06; 185; 1 box (Box 11)
    Bradley
  - Baccalaureate, 1996 June 06; 191; 1 box (Box 11)
  - Commencement, 1996 June 06; 1785; 1 box (Box 42)
    Straight on camera
  - 1996 Commencement, undated; 1130; 1 box (Box 4)
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 March 06; 133; 1 box (Box 11)
    Mahoney The applied sciences at Princeton
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 March 28; 162; 1 box (Box 11)
    J. Jefferson Looney Early history of the American Whig and Cliosophic societies
  - Cold War - Session 1, 1996 March 29; 1194; 1 box (Box 4)
    Tape #2 of 2
  - Cold War - Session 1, 1996 March 29; 1199; 1 box (Box 4)
    Tape #1 of 2
  - Cold War - Session 2, 1996 March 29; 1195; 1 box (Box 55)
    Tape #1 of 1
  - Cold War - Session 3, 1996 March 30; 1196; 1 box (Box 4)
  - Cold War - Session 4, 1996 March 30; 1197; 1 box (Box 4)
    Tape # 1 of 1
  - Cold War Session 4, 1996 March 30; 1198; 1 box (Box 55)
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 May 02; 147; 1 box (Box 11)
    Arthur S. Wightman The exact sciences at Princeton
  - Whig Hall 1995 Renovation, 1995 July 01; 1323; 1 box (Box 56)
  - Lecture, 1996 November 12; 1115; 1 box (Box 25)
    Dr. Daniel Rubenstein: Natural History
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 November 14; 142; 1 box (Box 11)
    Whiteman
  - 250th Anniversary Lecture, 1996 November 14; 1118; 1 box (Box 25)
    Whiteman McCosh 10
  - Lecture, 1996 October 03; 1110; 1 box (Box 4)
    John T. Bonner
  - Arthur Miller, 1996 October 10; 1914; 1 box (Box 63)
    Belknap Lecture
  - CTN Gavel to Gavel, 1996 October 03; 1139; 1 box (Box 26)
    Joint Session of the 207th Legislature
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 October 10; 177; 1 box (Box 11)
    John Murrin Princeton and the Rise of Inter-Collegiate Athletics
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 October 12; 166; 1 box (Box 11)
    Mark A. Noll The founding era of the College of NJ
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 October 24; 137; 1 box (Box 11)
    Tony Grafton
  - Campus Shots, 1996 October 24; 1656; 1 box (Box 39)
    ESL students getting lesson
  - 250th Convocation, 1996 October 25; 126; 1 box (Box 11)
  - Charter Day, 1996 October 25; 1236; 1 box (Box 30)
    250th Anniversary Tape #1
  - Charter Day, 1996 October 25; 1237; 1 box (Box 30)
    250th Anniversary Tape #2. Toni Morrison
  - Charter Day, 1996 October 25; 1653; 1 box (Box 39)
    Cutaway shots of Convocation Tape1
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, 1996 October 25; 1655; 1 box (Box 39)
    Interview at outdoor celebration
  - Campus Shots, 1996 October 25; 1657; 1 box (Box 39)
    Reunions - Interviews with alumni, ice carving
  - Charter Day Convocation, 1996 October 25; 1685; 1 box (Box 40)
    Cutaway Shots Tape 2
  - Fireworks/Marshalls, 1996 October 25; 1692; 1 box (Box 40)
  - A tribute to the performing arts, 1996 October 26; 141; 1 box (Box 11)
  - Lecture, 1996 October 27; 165; 1 box (Box 11)
    Cornel West: Prophecy and social criticism 2 tapes
  - Sex on a Saturday night, 1996 September 10; 209; 1 box (Box 12)
  - 250th Lecture Series of The Graduate School, 1996 September 26; 140; 1 box (Box 11)
    The town of Princeton and the university
  - Princeton University's 250th Anniversary, undated; 1658; 1 box (Box 39)
    Luthier Standup talking about the 250th celebration
  - Looking Back: Reflections of Black Princeton Alumni, 1997 April 02; 1136; 1 box (Box 25)
    1:15
  - Looking Back: Reflections of Black Princeton Alumni, 1997 April 02; 1238; 1 box (Box 30)
  - Hitler's willing executioners: Ordinary Germans and the holocaust, 1997 April 06; 152; 1 box (Box 11)
    Daniel Jonah Goldhagen
  - Early Childhood Education Panel Discussion, 1997 April 25; 1140; 1 box (Box 26)
  - Early Childhood Education, 1997 April 25; 1149; 1 box (Box 27)
    Hilary Clinton - Keynote Speaker
  - Early Childhood Education, 1997 April 25; 1674; 1 box (Box 40)
    Hillary Clinton Tape 2
  - Magic Show, 1997 February 20; 18; 1 box (Box 6)
    Christo and Jean Claude
  - Public Lecture, 1997 February 20; 122; 1 box (Box 11)
    No Audio
  - Lecture, 1997 February 25; 183; 1 box (Box 11)
    Steele
  - MLK tribute, 1997 January 20; 115; 1 box (Box 11)
  - 1997 Baccalaureate, 1997 June 01; 1232; 1 box (Box 30)
  - Commencement, 1997 June 03; 167; 1 box (Box 11)
  - CREN Spot, 1997 May 08; 1219; 1 box (Box 29)
    Ira Fuchs
  - 250th Birthday Musicals, 1997 May 14; 116; 1 box (Box 11)
  - Jimmy Stewart, 1997 May 30; 1243; 1 box (Box 5)
    Jimmy Stewart Theater dedication ceremony Best edited version
  - Sex On A Saturday Night, 1997 September 10; 1224; 1 box (Box 55)
  - Sex On A Saturday Night, 1997 September 10; 1230; 1 box (Box 55)
  - S.E.T.I. Lecture, 1998 April 07; 1244; 1 box (Box 55)
  - Lecture, 1998 April 15; 19; 1 box (Box 6)
  - Alumni Council, 1998 August 03; 198; 1 box (Box 11)
    Silver
  - Lecture, 1998 December 02; 21; 1 box (Box 6)
    Marcus Raichle
  - Lecture, 1998 December 03; 7; 1 box (Box 6)
    Dede Meyers
  - Lecture, 1998 December 10; 8; 1 box (Box 6)
    Jane Goodall
  - Commencement, 1998 June 02; 1665; 1 box (Box 39)
    Tape 1 of 2
  - Commencement, 1998 June 02; 1666; 1 box (Box 39)
    Tape 2 of 2
  - Lecture, 1998 June 18; 11; 1 box (Box 6)
    Governor Whitman
  - Building Dedication, 1998 May 18; 1150; 1 box (Box 27)
    Lyman Spitzer
  - NSTX Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1998 May 18; 1151; 1 box (Box 27)
  - Lyman Spitzer Plague, 1998 May 18; 1229; 1 box (Box 30)
  - McDonnell Hall Dedication, 1998 May 29; 1667; 1 box (Box 39)
  - Baccalaureate, 1998 May 31; 1669; 1 box (Box 39)
  - Baccalaureate, 1998 May 31; 1670; 1 box (Box 39)
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 05; 1144; 1 box (Box 26)
    Jose Ramos-Horta. Welcome and "Democracy and Diplomacy in the Asia Pacific Region. Program #1. 57:15
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 05; 1145; 1 box (Box 26)
    Betty Williams. Children's Rights: The need to establish safe havens for children of war. Program #2. 61:30
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 05; 1146; 1 box (Box 26)
    Rigoberta Menchu Tum. The role of indigenous people in a democratic Guatemala. Program #3. 57:45
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 05; 1148; 1 box (Box 27)
    Archbishop Desmond Tutu. Reconciliation in Post-Apartheid South Africa: Experiences of the Truth Commission. Program #4. 60:30
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 06; 1147; 1 box (Box 26)
    Harn Yawnghwe on behalf of Aung San Suu Kyi. The UN Declaration of human rights and its impact on Asian values and democratic principles. Program6
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 06; 1158; 1 box (Box 27)
    Former President Oscar Arias Sanchez. International code of conduct for arms transfers. Program #5. 56:00
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 06; 1159; 1 box (Box 27)
    Bobby Muller. The Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation and the International Campaign to Ban Landmines. Program #7. 48:45
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 06; 1160; 1 box (Box 28)
    Jody Williams. International Organization in the International Campaign to Ban Landmines. Program #8. 52:30
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 06; 1161; 1 box (Box 28)
    His Holiness the Dalai Lama. The need for compassion in society: The case of Tibet. Program #9. 59:00
  - Nobel Peace Laureates Conference, 1998 November 06; 1162; 1 box (Box 28)
    Concluding remarks by President John Casteen, UVA. Press Conference. Program #10. 41:35
  - Lecture, 1998 November 19; 22; 1 box (Box 6)
    Persi Diaconis
  - Memorial Service, 1998 October 25; 1141; 1 box (Box 26)
    Betacam Sp
    Carl Fields Tape 2 of 2
  - Memorial Service, 1998 October 25; 1142; 1 box (Box 26)
    Carl Fields Tape 1 0f 2
  - Lecture, 1998 October 26; 10; 1 box (Box 6)
    Jon Gordon
  - Lecture, 1998 October 27; 5; 1 box (Box 6)
    Lori B Andrews
  - Cloning, 1998 October 28; 4; 1 box (Box 6)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1998 September 13; 6; 1 box (Box 6)
  - Sex On A Saturday Night, 1998 September 16; 1216; 1 box (Box 55)
  - Sex On A Saturday Night, 1998 September 16; 1228; 1 box (Box 55)
  - Stadium Dedication, 1998 September 19; 12; 1 box (Box 6)
  - Public Lecture Series, 1999 April 06; 30; 1 box (Box 7)
    Thomas Eisner
  - Bill Moyer's Mind, Faith, and Spirit, 1999 April 08; 31; 1 box (Box 7)
    Bill Moyer's Mind, Faith, and Spirit
  - Mind, Faith, and Spirit with Bill Moyers, 1999 April 08; 1169; 1 box (Box 28)
    Bill Moyers Tape 1 of 2
  - Mind, Faith, and Spirit with Bill Moyers, 1999 April 08; 1170; 1 box (Box 28)
    Bill Moyers Tape 2 of 2
  - Public Lecture Series, 1999 April 19; 34; 1 box (Box 7)
    Paul Muldoon
  - Sex On a Saturday Night, 1999 April 21; 28; 1 box (Box 7)
  - Public Lecture Series, 1999 December 01; 46; 1 box (Box 7)
    Paul Krugman
  - Alumni Studies, 1999 December 03; 47; 1 box (Box 7)
  - Lecture, 1999 February 03; 35; 1 box (Box 7)
    Frankenthaler. No audio
  - Toni Morrison Conference, 1999 February 12; 24; 1 box (Box 6)
    Toni Morrison Conference. 6 tapes from 2/12 and 2/13
  - Public Lecture Series, 1999 February 25; 33; 1 box (Box 7)
    Itmar Rabinovich
  - Lecture, 1999 January 11; 9; 1 box (Box 6)
    Harold Pinter
  - MLK, 1999 January 18; 23; 1 box (Box 6)
  - Georgia Nugent's Managers Orientation PMI, 1999 June 23; 26; 1 box (Box 7)
    Georgia Nugent's Managers Orientation PMI
  - Public Lecture Series, 1999 March 04; 32; 1 box (Box 7)
    Ingrid Daubechies
  - Lecture, 1999 May 04; 25; 1 box (Box 7)
    Martin Scorcese 2 tapes
  - Alumni Lectures, 1999 May 08; 20; 1 box (Box 6)
    4 tapes from 5/7 and 5/8
  - Baccalaureate, 1999 May 30; 252; 1 box (Box 12)
  - Baccalaureate, 1999 May 30; 1668; 1 box (Box 39)
  - 1999 Commencement, undated; 1268; 1 box (Box 5)
  - Lecture, 1999 November 16; 29; 1 box (Box 7)
    Margery Garber
  - Public Lecture Series, 1999 November 16; 45; 1 box (Box 7)
    Marjorie Garber 3 tapes
  - Lecture, 1999 November 22; 36; 1 box (Box 7)
    Robert McNeil
  - Public Lecture Series, 1999 October 04; 37; 1 box (Box 7)
    Andrew Knoll on evolution
  - Lecture, 1999 October 08; 38; 1 box (Box 7)
    Walesa
  - Debate, 1999 October 12; 39; 1 box (Box 7)
    Singer
  - Debate, 1999 October 12; 1662; 1 box (Box 39)
    Peter Singer and Adrienne Asch Tape 1 of 2
  - Debate, 1999 October 12; 1663; 1 box (Box 39)
    Peter Singer and Adrienne Asch Debate Tape 2 of 2
  - Lecture, 1999 October 13; 40; 1 box (Box 7)
    A. Blinder
  - Lecture, 1999 October 21; 41; 1 box (Box 7)
    Adrienne Rich
  - Freshman Orientation, 1999 September 29; 27; 1 box (Box 7)
    3 tapes. 1 SVHS and 2 VHS